please welcome Nicky places Nikki Glaser
Nikki Glaser the host with the most
steps tools in your apartment David
you've seriously influenced so many
female comics haircuts tonight jeff has
dressed as Prince the Prince of Wales
the animal you're fat
Jeff if you changed your name to
assemble and be the Arby's logo no Jeff
I'll admit I've imagined Jeff without
clothes it's how I stay thin
Rob Riggle I want to thank you so much
for fighting the war against terrorism
and subtlety Jimmy a car is what Ralph
Macchio has to do to find a place to
sleep every night
jewel is here or as I call her trailer
Swift's
jool I do not want a bad Matthews since
God already dead
I think your smile is cute I feel like
your teeth are like the Spice Girls you
know they're all different colors and
they're like doing their own things fun
[Applause]
Peyton Manning is here that's not for
you guys that's for him Peyton you're
here right now you've had a lot of
concussions you're here don't murder
your wife I I don't know much about
football but I love Peyton in
commercials you're like you're so good
at him like legitimately I'd say you're
the greatest of all time I'd say like
you like the Tom Brady of being in
commercials you know like the greatest
like he's the greatest right so and
without furor adieu and Coulter
oh and what's it like to be like a
real-life supervillain
you know like I'd ask you how you sleep
at night but I'd assume just upside down
in a robe of 101 dalmatians and Colter
has written 11 books 12 if you count
mine comps
yes ansmann cold things like a racist
anti-semitic homophobic a white
supremacist and that's just while
getting plowed by Bill Maher the only
person you will ever make happy is the
Mexican who digs your grave speaking of
Hitler Jeff you and Hitler have a lot in
common
what's micropenis you're bad at your art
and no one cared about you till you
started roasting people guys I can make
that joke because I'm not Jewish so I
don't care
don't be mad at least I acknowledge the
Holocaust and doesn't even think it
happens
speaking of deniable tragedies rob lowe
I can't see it I'm Rob defies age
restrictions you really you're you're
honest look at you you look like you're
sculpted I mean you put the statue in
statutory rape I mean right god I had
such a crush on you when I was a little
girl if only I'd known that's when I had
my best shot thank you so much
[Applause]
he's so cute so adorable I bet you eat
but only with the crusts cut off
first
if that is luck speaking of crusty
I'll get to you in a second Sybil I am I
[Applause]
know Martha Stewart thank you for being
here seriously and congratulations on
getting that tie soccer team out of your
vagina
and into your sweatshops that's where
they are now surprisingly Martha said
that prison food wasn't that bad just
you know as long as it was clean-shaven
so she loves attention to detail is she
laughing
I'm terrified of her no I honestly
Martha sir I'm a huge fan and my mom is
even bigger fit my mom has learned
everything from Martha Stewart about
cooking and cleaning and withholding
affection so close to my heart
Kevin is here such an amazing
actor most I know Kevin is like one of
the greatest Impressionists of all time
I'm a huge fan my favorite of his is he
does an amazing Robin Williams I just
wish you would finish it yeah okay guys
listen all I'm saying is that we've lost
a lot of greats to suicide recently and
it's time we lose some okay's symbols
gorgeous I'm like honored to meet her
and and to her resume is insane like if
you look at it it's just like model
actor singer you name it she's dead
I don't know any of these people Sybil
why am I here Oh literally you have like
no friends
it's truly so cool to be sharing the
stage with these badass women
Cybill Shepherd Martha Stewart Margaret
Cho
I'm sorry Dahmer era I'm sorry
I thought that was dumb a rare I know
you sleepy potato
Tom I love you but how did you have a
stroke on both sides of your face
explain that they don't get it Dennis
Rodman of course not Dennis just earlier
tonight when he tried to sell me incense
on the sidewalk
I don't want any okay
Edward Norton is here anybody and looks
to me like if a marionette became a boy
and then that boy became an
right he was so hot in Fight Club right
when he was Brad Pitt that was not
now let's get to Bruce Bruce this is
honestly a real a big personal moment
for me to be here roasting my dead
cousins second favorite action star I
know you obviously as the star of every
DVD you kind of just find on the street
obviously you had an amazing action film
career until Jason Statham started
balding I'm just not familiar with
action movie I don't know I've never
seen a single one of your films
consensually like it's always what some
guy puts on while he's trying to finger
me on his roommates couch soon saying
maybe I didn't understand the Fifth
Element and it wasn't cuz I'm a dumb
girl but because it's hard to follow
that plot when you're fighting off a
roofie and there's a knuckle inside you
you know just be oh I love this Sixth
Sense though I loved in the ending when
the guy came in my eye and I didn't have
to watch the rest of it that was great a
lot of people don't know that Bruce is a
very talented musician because he isn't
Bruce has also been very active with the
make-a-wish Foundation which is where
they make sick kids meet you so dying
doesn't seem so terrible so Bruce
in all honesty thank you for having me
here you're really cool
you're so hot and and this is a special
night you really are it's a special
night obviously your families and your
daughters must be so proud of their
father Ashton Kutcher thank you very
much good night
[Applause]
keep it going for the reason Mike Pence
says we have hurricanes you look like
the little man on top of a wedding cake
that a bakery would refuse to make for
you
Will and Grace was really the best you
could do it just
[Applause]
just jack just jack is uh it's also what
I'm gonna do in my hotel room alone
after sitting next to Blake Griffin all
night Jesus Christ
[Applause]
you're so I'd you in front of my
grandparents I that's how
I almost want to you know I feel like
Mimi would be proud
like you look like a black guy that got
made by a printer running out of ink
that's
[Applause]
Chris Redd is here because Comedy
Central wasn't sure if Blake was black
or not
you look great Chris you was dressed
like a nine-year-old who just found a
thousand dollars on the sidewalk
at this point like what can we say about
Jeff Ross that he hasn't heard before
it's like oh I respect you
you look nice tonight here's your salad
sir stuff like that okay Jeff you look
like if pop I only ate Popeyes check
that
no Jeff no don't break the couch your
face your face has a dad bod let's
Jeff gets really hot girls and I just I
don't how do you get tens teens I'm
sorry I read that wrong how do you get
you have the sex appeal of a gymnastics
doctor I just don't understand
robert de niro is here
looking like else
[Applause]
I can't even believe I get to share this
stage with you tonight Roberts narrow
and by this stage I mean the final one
of your life it's
I'm sorry I don't feel right about any
of this
Caitlyn Jenner I just want to thank you
for all you've done for the trans
movement in the size 16 stiletto
industry you are such an incredible
athlete people forget just how fast you
once ran from your first family to go be
on a reality show
seriously though I know being a new mom
is hard
[Applause]
but even Casey Anthony knows the current
location of her daughter
[Applause]
okay you're a Republican I don't know
why you've already gained control over a
woman's body
what does that party have to do to lose
your support of be your son
kaitlin I know you've only publicly
identified as a woman for a few years
but I just want you to know that I know
that deep down you have always been a
and I spelled with a k though for you
you're great thank you you're great Alec
Baldwin what an honor to be here
roasting Justin Bieber's wife's oldest
fattest uncle it's like I'll never
forget that voicemail that when you
called your daughter Ireland a
thoughtless little pig I tell you one of
the worst things you can call your
daughter after Ireland actually that's
that name
yikes speaking of terrible names your
wife's name is hilarious is it hilarya
hello it's hilarious Laura Neal our
Hilaria oh it's so stupid okay it
doesn't matter she's so hot dude she's
so hot and fit just getting screamed at
burn calories
you have four kids under the age of six
I just how do you do it I mean isn't
your semen just oatmeal at this point Oh
Robert just got excited when I said ode
meal he's sort of salivating your night
nurse is warming it up backstage it'll
be ready in the break I'm such a fan of
the Baldwin's I've never been so sure
that four people have buried a hooker
together in all seriousness I want to
thank Alec in his memoir he bravely
admitted that he had once considered
suicide and I just want to say that that
meant a lot to me because I have also
considered your suicide and I have some
ideas I even know what I'm gonna wear
alik thank you so much for having me
here tonight
[Applause]
[Music]